<resources>
    <string name="app_name"> Football Match Live TV Score</string>
    <string name="channel_1">https://www.twitch.tv/</string>
    <string name="strimming">Live streaming Football</string>
    <string name="footballguide">Live Football Guide</string>
    <string name="livetvscore">Football Live TV Score</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="load">reload</string>
    <string name="agree_next">Agree &amp; Next</string>
    <string name="number_picker_formatter">%02d</string>


    <string name="aa1">Live Football Live Score Poppy is an original short Poppy platform for people to share their stories and showcase their talent. Live Football Live Score Poppy empowers users with easy-to-use Poppy editing tools, cute stickers and special effects to capture vivid moments for sharing and to connect with people in the Live Football Live Score Poppy community with similar interests</string>
    <string name="aa2">Step 1: - First of all, install the Live Football Live Score Poppy app in your android mobile.\10 Step 2: - After installing Live Football Live Score Poppy app you will have many Poppy shows of like. Would like to download Live Football Live Score Poppy . Click on that Poppy , then the Poppy will open.</string>
    <string name="aa3">Live Football Live Score Poppy is not safe for younger kids, and even teens who fit the age recommendation of the app should be monitored with a watchful eye.</string>
    <string name="aa4">Live Football Live Score Poppy is not safe for younger kids, and even teens who fit the age recommendation of the app should be monitored with a watchful eye.</string>

    <string name="bb">Welcome to IPL 2022 Tips IPL 2022 Show is accessible in all the world, and has more than 28,000 hours of video content that incorporates appears from channels like MTV, Nicklodeon and colors.</string>
    <string name="bb1">IPL 2022 is an Indian subscription video on demand (SVOD) service. Launched in March 2016, forms the online arm of Viacom 18. It is Viacom18 s advertising-led video-on-demand platform that is available as an app for iOS, Kaios (Jiophone) and Android users, and a website for desktop consumption. IPL 2022 is available only in India, and hosts over 40,000 hours of video content that includes shows from channels like MTV, Nickelodeon and Colors. IPL2022Content is also available in multiple languages like Kannada, Marathi, Bengali, Gujarati and Tamil.</string>
    <string name="bb2">IPL 2022 has content from Colors TV, MTV India, Nickelodeon India and other Viacom 18 owned television channels. It also hosts many Bollywood films for streaming. It has produced several `IPL 2022 Original` shows for streaming as well. In the children`s segment, it is working on shows in Malayalam and Telugu.</string>
    <string name="bb3">Following are the channels owned by Viacom 18: 1. Colors Hindi 2. MTV 3. IPL 2022 Originals 4. Nickelodeon 5. Vhi 6. Colors Infinity 7. MTV Beats 8. Colors Telugu 9. Colors Kannada 10. Colors SUPER 11. Colors Tamil 12. Colors Marathi 13. Colors Bangla 14. Colors Gujarathi 15. CNN-News18 16. Firstpost 17. News18 India 18. News18 Bangla 19. News18 Gujarati 20. News18 UP Uttarakhand 21. News18 MP Chhattisgarh 22. News18 Rajasthan 23. News18 Bihar Jharkhand 24. IPL 2022 eSports 25. VICE</string>
    <string name="bb4">Following are the shows only hosted by IPL 2022: 1. Chinese Bhasads 2. Soadies 3. Sinskaari 4. Badman 5. Shaadi Boys 6. It`s Not That Simple 7. Untag 8. Yo Ke Hua Bro 9. Time Out 10. Silsila Badalte Rishton Ka 11. Stupid Man Smart Phone 12. Feet Up With The Stars 13. Shortcuts 14. Its Not That Simple 15. Fuh Se Fantasy</string>
    <string name="bb5">What`s the catch? Well, IPL 2022 is an IPL 2022ad-supported platform, which means you`ll have to deal with the occasional advertisement popping up during your binge-watch sessions. UtilsIPI can be annoying, but they`re a small price to pay for access to IPL 2022`s impressive content catalogue</string>
    <string name="bb6">What`s the catch? Well, IPL 2022 is an IPL 2022ad-supported platform, which means you`ll have to deal with the occasional advertisement popping up during your binge-watch sessions. UtilsIPI can be annoying, but they`re a small price to pay for access to IPL 2022`s impressive content catalogue</string>
    <string name="bb7">Unlike rivals like Netflix and Amazon, which are available on everything from computers to game consoles, IPL 2022 keeps things simple. Users can access the platform via the web using a laptop or PC, or download the IPL 2022 app on their mobile device (smartphone or tablet) from the App Store or Google Play. On the same note, the service is available on the big screen as well, so you can watch your favourite shows and movies in style. You can use Chromecast or Fire TV to access IPL 2022 content on your television. The list of compatible devices is expected to grow in the future, with IPL 2022 currently working on developing apps for Windows phones, Apple TV and Android TV.</string>
    <string name="bb8">Watch live IPL 2022 show TV on your device! This Mobile TV app loads a database of TV channels compatible with your mobile device. Simply choose a TV channel, click play icon and watch TV wherever you are whenever you want for free! Guide for IPL 2022 show tv Channels App provides you a more than list of all Jio tv live Channels with Channel Number, Jio TV allows you to watch Live TV channels  past 7 days programs on any device, any time. We have got all your favourite channels : Colors, Star TV, Star Plus, Star Sports, Star Movies Select, Life OK, Movies OK, Asianet, Suvarna, Sony Sab, Sony MAX, Sony MIX, Sony Pal, Sony ESPN, Sony Six, IPL 2022 TV, TV.</string>
    <string name="bb9">All Shows 1760 Saasumaa 1760 Sasubai 2MAD Aa Family Comedy Che Aaj Kay Special Aali Lahar Kela Kahar Aamchya Gharaat Sunbai Jorat Aawaz Abbulish Agnisakshi Live IPL 2022 show Tv Guide is a tutorial and guide application that teach you how to Watch Live TV, Movies, Live ISL channels, Live big boss, Kids Shows, News, Comedy Clips, Catch-up, Video on Demand (VOD), Originals, Music and much more in all different languages - English, Arabic, French, Spanish, Russian, Japanese, Korean, Chinese, Urdu, Hindi, Tamil, Telugu.</string>
    <string name="bb10">All Shows 1760 Saasumaa 1760 Sasubai 2MAD Aa Family Comedy Che Aaj Kay Special Aali Lahar Kela Kahar Aamchya Gharaat Sunbai Jorat Aawaz Abbulish Agnisakshi Live IPL 2022 show Tv Guide is a tutorial and guide application that teach you how to Watch Live TV, Movies, Live ISL channels, Live big boss, Kids Shows, News, Comedy Clips, Catch-up, Video on Demand (VOD), Originals, Music and much more in all different languages - English, Arabic, French, Spanish, Russian, Japanese, Korean, Chinese, Urdu, Hindi, Tamil, Telugu.</string>
    <string name="disconnected">Connect VPN to get fast and reliable service.</string>
    <string name="privacy">      By clicking you are Agreeing to  <font fgcolor="#4196F8">Privacy Policy</font>\n                            and <font fgcolor="#4196F8">Terms &amp; Conditions</font></string>

    <string name="privacy_brief">Terms Of Use</string>
    <string name="condition">Posting rules you should be taking care of before you start interaction on our website/application:
\n Assuring you carry the rights and eligibility to post any form of content you are about to share.
        \nWe never permit nudism on application/website.We won\'t allow posting of sexually explicit content,
        \nsexually explicit text, images, or audio content depicting extreme sexual acts such as acts of posting Content that drives traffic to pornographic online services.
        \nPlease note that we may make exceptions based on artistic, educational, historical, documentary, or scientific nature,
        \nor where there are other considerable benefits to the public at large.
\nWe don\'t permit encouragement or applaud towards terrorism, formed crime scenes or hate association groups on our application/website.
        \nAttempting to sell sexual services or weapons and harmful drugs are also not permitted. We will remove reasonable threats of severity,
        \nhate arousing content/speech and the intentionally pointing of private individuals. We do not permit attacks/abuse based on skin colour, native, sex, gender, gender identity, sexual orientation, religion, disability or disease.
\nGraphic violence is not allowed and we may remove videos or images of intense, graphic violence to make sure our application/website stays appropriate for everyone.
\nIf anyone or any account is spotted doing the above restricted activities they can be booked and arrested for the same.
        \nIf viewers spot any violations of the above rules they have the right to report the content to us by using the report feature given in our application/ website.</string>


</resources>